Guide to the Robert J. Havighurst Papers 1921-1991
University of Chicago Library
- Series XII: Adulthood, Aging, and the Life Cycle
  - Subseries 4: Gerontology
    - NCOA Policy-Student Center (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Kaplan-Leisure (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - NCOA Before 1973 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - NCOA-Current (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Ringo (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Clark Foundation. (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Policy Issues (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Parnes-Ohio State (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - 1981 Conference Aging, Miscellaneous Reserve (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - MCCOA Reserve (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Int. Committee on Ger. (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - Indian Study (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - Harris Poll, 1981 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Program of Study Form (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - NCOA Policy Com, 1978 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - National Council on the Aging, Ageism and the Harris Poll (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Randal Awards (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Ahrens-NCOA (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - NCOA Folder (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Humanities, NCOA (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - NCOA (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - NCOA Children and Elderly (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - NCOA Monograph on Education and the Harris Poll (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - NCOA Envelope (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Harris Poll (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - NCOA-Res. Committee (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - NCOA Statement (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Community for Elderly People Proposal (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Family Relations (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Family Project, 1981 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Family IHC Proposal (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - NSF Russell Family MS (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - NCOA (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Transitions in Human Development (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Ger. Ris and Aging (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - R and F (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Article Forthcoming (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - White House Conference on Aging (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Quality of Life in Later Years (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - White House Conference, Pendell Paper (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Chapter IV (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - White House Planning, Agenda Conference (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1971 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - WHCOA-Post Conference Board (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Post White House Conference on Aging (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Retirement in Four Professions (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Reports on the Committee on Later Maturity (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Memorandum on Individual and Social Factors in the Problem of Retirement (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Ghottes Reserve (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - White House Conf. On Aging, Training and Research in Aging (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Illinois Consortium for Gerontology (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Ill Conference on Aging (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - MOSC Current (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - MOSC 1980 (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Office for Senior Citizens and Handicapped (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Service Provision (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - Service Providers Committee-MOSC (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - Service Providers-MOSC (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Byrne-MOSC (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - MOSC Reserve 1979 (Box 188, Folder 18)
    - Politics and PR (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - RTA Group 1977-1979 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Service Providers, 1978 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Proposal re: Gerontology (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Suburban Cook County Survey (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - MOSC-General Correspondence (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - MOSC-1974 Material (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Sr. Center-Extended Evaluation (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Council on Aging, City of Chicago (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - RJH, 1981 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - MOSC (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - ENOA Current 1980 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Ed. Needs and Status of Older Adults in Illinois (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Illinois State Study, Business Proposal (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Illinois State Study Background (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Chi Reports-RA (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Chicago Interview (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Q’Aire Background (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Research-Ethnic Study (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - ENOA-1979-1984 Business (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Dean’s Conference Dec 12, 1978-Network Ed Task Force (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Network Board, Oct 1978-Autumn 1979 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Network Personnel Committee, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Network Research Committee, Miscellaneous (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Center for Retired Professionals, Univ. Extension (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Committee on Adult Education (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Education Network for Older Adults, Board Meeting, 1978 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Network Reserve (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Education Task Force (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Network for Older Adults (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Copy of Original Ed Network Proposal for the File (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Network Committees, Spring 1978 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Buchmann Ed. Network (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Revision of Reminiscence Questionnaire (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Reminiscence Study (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - For RJH (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - APA Aging Symposium (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Metaphor (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Reminiscence Study (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Time Study (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Guideline for a Diary on Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - RJH: Research Application NIH Exploratory Study of Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - Functions and Content of Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Interest -Morris (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - Groups and Word MA Papers (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - Reminiscence (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - Public Housing Sampling Lists (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - Reminiscence (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Public Housing Sample Lists (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Data (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Work Sheets (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Reliability Test (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Taft (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Applegate, Anita (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Rem Paper-Sent to: (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Small Grant Application (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Rem Scales, etc. (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Rem Paper, 1971-1972 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Rem. Data (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Life Review and Reminiscence (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - 1970 Rem. Data (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - George (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Productivity Measures (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Coding (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Ch 1 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Data on Educators and other samples (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Activity Rating Scales, 65-70 and 70+ (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Impact (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Madden and Fillenbaum (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Patton (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Post-Retirement: The Use of Human Potential (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Tables and Ditto Educators (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Stress Study (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Education Policy (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Other Questionnaires (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Productivity and Background (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Questionnaire C (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Productivity (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Coding and Scoring Manual for the Study of Reminiscence (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - OWU 21 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Class of ’23 printout and letter (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Ohio Welsyan Alumni Table (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Questions for OWU (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - OWU MC (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Articles for OWU Magazine (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - OWU Survey (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Data Sheets (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Ohio Weslyan Book Ideas (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Worksheets (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - OWU Analysis of Data (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Big City Public Schools (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - OWU Letters (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Life after 60 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Questionnaire-Life after 60 (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Thomas Pope Property and Productivity (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Protection of Human Subjects (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - Mailings to Scholars and Administrators (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - People Who Send in Material (Box 194, Folder 19)
    - Lives after 60-Letters to Respondents (Box 194, Folder 20)
    - Master List (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Respondents (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Ill 917 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - 910 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - McDonald (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - 1172 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Lives After 60-Copies Mailed (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Social Scientists and Educators (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Requests for Summary Report (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - APA Symposium (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Final Report on Productivity Study (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Heiss (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Snow, MA Paper (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Snow, Robert (High Level Productivity Study) (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - AAAS Symposium (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - NSF Research Proposal (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Time Consumption (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - McDonald Sample Diss. (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - UPI RM (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - SPI-Scoring (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - SPI (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - SPI Ed. (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Q-Sat. (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Self-Sort (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - The Questionnaire (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Instruments (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Life After 60 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - SPI (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - SS-New Directions (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - OCCE Study (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Ratings Institutions (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - High Level Productivity (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Lifestyle Types and Patterns of Retirement of Educators (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Paper on Educators (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Lifestyle Patterns (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Global Ratings (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Educators-New Data (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Educators Sub. (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - Snow-Paper (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - Patterns of Change (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Imagery (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Raw Data on Production (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Chapters 1-2 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Institutes, Data (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Educators, Ch IV Data (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Education (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Data, Educators (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Educators (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Male Social Scientists (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Leo Maulen (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Joe Mazel (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Male SS Old Paper (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Res Plans and Pub Plans (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - AERA (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Life Course of Academicians (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Pamela Perun 1976-77 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Perun Academic Women (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Perun 1979 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Pam Thesis RA (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Pam’s Paper (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Optional Questions: Pam (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - 908 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - 558 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Letters (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - 162 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - 099 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - 164 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Productivity (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Letters (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Academic Women Social Scientists and Retirement (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Study of Late Life Professional Visibility and Academic Activity of Male Social Scientists (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Personality and Aging Book (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Patterns of Aging (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Chapter II (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Chapter IV (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - BN VB Project (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 1 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Chapter VI (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Chapter VIII (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Chapter IX (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Personality Typing (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Chapter VII (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Reliability of Disengagement Ratings (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - HP’s Other Parts (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Chapter III (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Chapter V (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Lifestyles and Patterns of Aging (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Appendix II and III: Interview Schedule (Retired Steelworkers) (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Successful Aging, Definition and Measurement (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Ger. Sa. Los Angeles Meeting, Paper, etc. (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Chapter II (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - MSS for Bon on Patterns (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Crossculture Aging Publication Agreement (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Des. The. On x-nat’l study (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Tobia-Book (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Disengagement and Patterns of Aging (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Disengagement (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - LSIA-Life Satisfaction Index (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Subjective Well-Being (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - References on Life Satisfaction (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Successful Aging-RJH Reprint from The Gerontologist, Mar. (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Life Satisfaction Measurement (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Life Satisfaction (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Life Satisfaction Index (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Reed Larson Life Satisfaction (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Appendices: Adjustment to Retirement (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Activities and Attitudes (Box 201, Folder 10)
- Series XIII: Organizations
  - American Optometric Association (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Optometry (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Committee Mtg Jan 8-9, 1952 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Commission Letter Dtd 9/12/72 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Optometric Education (Box 201, Folder 15)
  - Publication (Box 201, Folder 16)
  - Disposition of Data (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Berrien County Early Reading (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Mailing List (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Initial Progress Report-Optometry (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Optometric Ed-Dickey, Frank G. National Commission on Accrediting (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - HOP Council on Accreditation (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Liaison Officers-Optometric Ed (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Faculty Members of Schools and Colleges of Optometry (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Persons Active in the Practice of Optometry (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaire for Optometric Faculty (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - Questionnaire for Practitioners-June 1972 (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - Consultants (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Ewalt, H. Ward (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - Optometric Center of New York (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - Haffner (Box 202, Folder 16)
  - Data, Ch. 2 (Box 202, Folder 17)
  - Hollinshead, Byron (Box 202, Folder 18)
  - Hopping, Richard (Box 202, Folder 19)
  - McKeown, Dr. Raymond M. (Box 202, Folder 20)
  - Tumblin, J.C., Optometric Ed. (Box 202, Folder 21)
  - Conferences of Practitioners (Box 202, Folder 22)
  - Discussion Topics and Questions (Box 202, Folder 23)
  - Midwest Conference of Practitioners (Box 202, Folder 24)
  - New England Conference of Practitioners (Box 202, Folder 25)
  - Florida Practitioners (Box 202, Folder 26)
  - Practitioner Qre. (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Seger-Las Vegas, Feb 27, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Data on Schools, 90 pts. (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Visual Condition of the Population (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Visual Condition of Children (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Brechler, Frederick (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Financing Optometric Ed. (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - National Study of Optometric Ed. (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - National Health Services (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Manpower (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Bibliography on Optometric Manpower (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Minnesota Manpower Survey (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - Minutes (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Optometric Practice (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - Research Needs in the Field of Optometry (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - Optometry (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - Curriculum: Optometric Education (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - Optometry and Medicine (Box 203, Folder 18)
  - Optometry in Great Britain (Box 203, Folder 19)
  - Model Corr. (Box 203, Folder 20)
  - Optometry-Education for the Profession (Box 203, Folder 21)
  - Optometric Education: A Summary Report (Box 203, Folder 22)
  - Optometry: Education for the Profession, Fodler 2: Clinical Trainee Slips (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Churches International Education Program (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ (1 of 2) (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ (2 of 2) (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Church and the Elderly (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Church and Public Education (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - National Council of Churches -1979-Church and Education (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - National Council of Churches-Ed. Project (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Religion (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - List of Tribes and Schools Receiving Self-Study Announcements (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Squib-Report on Education and Major Philanthropic Foundations (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Report on Foundations (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Paper (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Responses to the Foundations’ Report (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Gent. Outline (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence-Foundation Study (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Families Count (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Foundations Report, Current (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - File Commission (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Foundations, Questionnaire (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Foundation (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Ch. 1 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Foundation Advisory Committee (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Expenses-Foundation Study (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee on Research, Council on Foundations (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Foundations and Public Education (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Foundations-Interest Groups (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Foundations (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Ch. 1 (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Ch. 2-analysis of Education (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - Ch. 3 (1 of 2) (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Ch. 3 (2 of 2) (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Ch. 4 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Ch. 4 Evaluation (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Foundation. Critiques (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Ch. 5, Perspectives (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - 6-Rockefeller Foundation (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - 7-Russell Sage (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - 8-Carnegie Foundation (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - 9, Danforth (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - 11, Ford Foundation. (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Kellogg Foundation (Box 207, Folder 10)
- Series XIV: Social Issues and Policy
  - Civil Rights Speech Model (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - AC Freedom (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Childrens’ Rights (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Grant Foundation (Box 207, Folder 14)
  - Lilly Foundation (Box 207, Folder 15)
  - Mott Foundation (Box 207, Folder 16)
  - Appendices (Box 207, Folder 17)
  - Categories (Box 207, Folder 18)
  - General (Box 207, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 207, Folder 20)
  - Danforth Foundation (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Grant Foundation (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller-General Education Board Foundation Study (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - R. Sage Foundation (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Foundations (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for a Study of Educational Foundations (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Study of the Professions (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - 82-84 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - CSC (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - CSC Records (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - City Schools Committee, 1981 (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - CSC Rubin Resignation (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - Civil and Human Rights (Box 208, Folder 13)
  - Clyde Miller Correspondence (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - ISPI Human Rights Commission (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Broyles (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Segregation (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Civil Rights and Education (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Am. Civil Lib. (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - ACLU Correspondence (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - Discipline (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Disruptive Youth (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Program Committee, HPCC (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - NCARL, June 1978 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Plenary Citizens (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Biographical Information (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - CC to Defend Bill of Rights (1 of 2) (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - CC to Defend Bill of Rights (2 of 2) (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - CDBR Reserve 1978-1981 (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - CCDBR 1983 (Box 209, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - McCann Act (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - CCDBR 1963-1964 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - 1966-CCDBR (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Bill of Rights Foundation (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - CCDBR (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Frank Wilkinson (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - ILL Justice Foundation (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - NCARL (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - CCDBR Before 1970 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - CCDBR (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - Bill of Rights Foundation (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Stability Fund (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Council on Aging (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Ed (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - MCC of A-Metropolitan Chicago Coalition on Aging (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Retirement (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - HPK Commerce Conference (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Current Energy Com. (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - Energy Resources and the Future of Retirement Age Policy (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Human Behavior and Development in an Equilibrium Society (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Ethical Issues and Energy (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Energy 1975 (Box 211, Folder 14)
  - Energy and Cost of Living (Box 211, Folder 15)
  - RJH Energy (Box 211, Folder 16)
  - Energy Resources (Box 211, Folder 17)
  - Proposal For a Seminar on Human Development and Behavior in the Immediate Future (Box 211, Folder 18)
  - Energy 1976 (Box 211, Folder 19)
  - Tolley (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Energy Seminar (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - Mankind and the 21st Century (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - NOMOR Reserve (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - NOMOR Ad (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - NOMOR CAFF (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - NOMOR Reserve 1978-79 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - SANE 8728 (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - Roseland-David (Box 212, Folder 9)
  - Symposium (Box 212, Folder 10)
  - Urban League Reports (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Urban League Correspondence (Box 213, Folder 2)
- Series XV: Restricted
  - Grade sheets and evaluative student materials, 1959-1963 [Restricted until 2043] (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - Records for Havighurst’s personnel, 1960-1977 [Restricted until 2027] (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, A-E, 1981-1985 [Restricted until 2015] (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, F-L, 1964-1984 [Restricted until 2014] (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, M, 1972-1983 [Restricted until 2013] (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, N, 1977-1982 [Restricted until 2012] (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, O-S, 1966-1984 [Restricted until 2014] (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations and referee reports, T-Z, 1972-1981 [Restricted until 2011] (Box 214, Folder 8)